Search results will appear here...

* 
* 

* 
* 

Privacy Policy
==============

Your Privacy
------------

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
----------------------------------------------

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet. To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL http://www.google.com/privacy\_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, TheRightScoop.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

Adapex
------

When you use our website and enter your email address on our website (either to log in, or sign up for a newsletter, or similar), we may share with solution providers and its group companies information that we collect from you, such as your email (in hashed, pseudonymous form), IP address, or information about your browser or operating system, with any of the following, acting as “joint controllers” (as applicable and defined in the GDPR). This Site is affiliated with Adapex INC for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and Adapex INC will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. Learn more about Adapex’s data usage here. https://adapex.io/privacy-policy/

Collection of Personal Information
----------------------------------

When visiting TheRightScoop.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Links to third party Websites
-----------------------------

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

Changes to this Privacy Statement
---------------------------------

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of TheRightScoop.com then you may [contact us](http://www.therightscoop.com/contact-the-right-scoop/).

### SUBMIT A TIP

Have a news tip for The Right Scoop? Submit it using the form below:

### Subscribe via Email

NEW: Enter your email address into our new system to subscribe to The Right Scoop and receive notifications of new posts by email.

You can customize your email delivery when you confirm your subscription.  

Email Address 

    Subscribe

### Connect

### Login

### Places of Interest

The Right Scoop site design was handcrafted by [Rightly Designed](https://rightlydesigned.com/).

© The Right Scoop 2009-2024. All rights reserved.
